{
    "subject": "resource/The_Lost_World_of_Mr._Hardy",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Lost World of Mr. Hardy is a film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9198890328407288,
            "question": "Who directed 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7248251438140869,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7188494801521301,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6856744289398193,
            "question": "Is 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy' a real place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6650425791740417,
            "question": "What type of media is 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6495001912117004,
            "question": "Is 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy' based on a book or other work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5459418296813965,
            "question": "Where can I watch 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5175772309303284,
            "question": "What genre does 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47138264775276184,
            "question": "What year was 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46159568428993225,
            "question": "Has 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy' won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Lost World of Mr. Hardy is a film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5895_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5895_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5895_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch 'The Lost World of Mr. Hardy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5895_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5895_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, \"The Lost World of Mr. Hardy\" is indeed referred to as a \"documentary film\", a \"film by Andy Heathcote & Heike Bachelier\", and a \"new feature length Independent filmmakers\" created this movie. Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that \"The Lost World of Mr. Hardy is a film\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"The Lost World of Mr. Hardy\" is a film, with information provided about its creators and content, thus supporting the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}